Guide to the Albert Galloway Keller Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1907 Sep 16
1907 Dec 13
1908 Jun 8
1908 Jul 15
1908 Jul 22
1908 Jul 25
1908 Jul 29
1908 Aug 13
1908 Aug 15
1908 Aug 28
1908 Aug 31
1908 Sep 4
1908 Oct 10
1908 Dec 11
1909 Jan 8 (postcard fragment)
1909 May 8
1909 Jul 14
1909 Aug 11 w/envelope
1909 Sep 5
1909 Sep 29
1909 Oct 9 (postcard)
1909 Nov 23 (postcard)
1909 Aug ?
n.d. 7 ALS and 1 postcard
Nation (New York, N.Y.); Saturday evening post; Saturday Review of Books; Yale Review; Business; Education -- United States; Popular culture; World War, 1914-1918; Germany -- History -- 1933-1945; United States -- Politics and government -- 1933-1945; Educators; Sociologists; Sumner-Keller Collection; Angell, James Rowland, 1869-1949; Asakawa, Kan'ichi, 1873-1948; Bishop, Avard Longley, 1875-1932; Bourne, Edward Gaylord, 1860-1908; Bowman, Isaiah, 1878-1950; Chamberlain, John, 1903-1995; Cheney, Benjamin Austin, 1867-; Cheney, Howell; Chittenden, R. H. (Russell Henry), 1856-1943; Cross, Wilbur L. (Wilbur Lucius), 1862-1948; Cutler, James Elbert, 1876-1959; Daggett, David Lewis, 1820-1896; Dana, James Dwight, 1813-1895; Danaher, John Anthony, 1899-; Davie, Maurice R. (Maurice Rea), 1893-1964; Day, Clarence, 1874-1935; Day, George Parmly, 1876-1959; Donaldson, Norman Vaux, 1891-1964; Frankfurter, Felix, 1882-1965; Fuller, Clement Austin, 1873-; Garrison, Wendell Phillips, 1840-1907; Gherini, Ambrose; Glass, Carter, 1858-1946; Granite, Mark; Hart, Thomas C. (Thomas Charles), 1877-1971; Holt, Henry, 1840-1926; Holt, Lucius Hudson, 1881-1953; Hoover, Herbert, 1874-1964; Jackson, John Day, 1868-; Johnson, Allen, 1870-1931; Jones, Frederick Scheetz, 1862-1944; Keller, Albert Galloway, 1874-1956; Keller, Carl Tilden, 1872-; Keller, Caroline; Knollenberg, Bernhard, 1892-1973; Lawrence, William Ewart, 1892-; Leach, G. Sidney; Leavens, Dickson H.; Lee, Alfred McClung, 1906-; Lerner, Max, 1902-1992; Lewis, Sinclair, 1885-1951; Leyburn, James Graham; Luce, Henry Robinson, 1898-1967; Maddox, John Lee, 1878-; McGraw, Arthur B.; Mencken, H. L. (Henry Louis), 1880-1956; Mendell, Clarence W. (Clarence Whittlesey), 1883-1970; Moore, Barrington, 1913-2005; Mussolini, Benito, 1883-1945; Paavola, Edwin K.; Peter, Julius C.; Peter, William Frederick, 1883-1956; Phelps, William Lyon, 1865-1943; Read, Leonard E. (Leonard Edward), 1898-1983; Resor, Stanley; Rosenthal, Charles; Russell, Fletcher A.; Seymour, Charles, 1885-1963; Shaw, Ralph Martin, 1869-1947; Smith, Edward Dorland, 1875-; Smithley, Robert L.; Stokes, Anson Phelps, 1874-1958; Sumner, Jeannie Whittmore Elliott; Sumner, William Graham, 1840-1910; Taft, Horace Dutton, 1861-1943; Taft, Robert A. (Robert Alphonso), 1889-1953; Thurber, Charles H. (Charles Herbert), 1864-1938; Tinker, Chauncey Brewster, 1876-1963; Todd, Arthur James, 1878-1948; Troxell, Janet Camp; Vaill, Dudley Landon; Walworth, Arthur, 1903-2005; Wang, Chengting Thomas, 1882-1961; Ward, Artemus, 1834-1867; Alfred A. Knopf, Inc; William Graham Sumner Club; Yale University Press; Yale University -- Curricula; Yale University -- Faculty; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. Dept. of Sociology; Yale University. Office of the Secretary; Yale University. Treasurer
- Correspondence, 1898-(1900-1956)-1971; Series I; 6.0 linear feet (15 boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  The first part of this series includes Correspondence to Keller, and is arranged alphabetically by writer. The second part of this series includes Correspondence not to Keller, and is also arranged alphabetically by writer.
  (*) Asterisks on folder listings indicate ten or more letters from a single correspondent. Folders containing two or more authors indicate less significant correspondence. Many correspondents may appear within a folder, but only the first and last correspondent will appear in the folder listing.
  - Abelson, Nathaniel O. -- Adams, Donald, 1927, 1936-1942, 1945, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Aiken, Edward E., Jr. -- Allen, Phillip R., 1913-1914, 1916, 1932, 1934, 1942, 1944, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science -- The American Mercury, 1914-1916, 1935, 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The American Mercury (Box 1, Folder 3)
    General note
    See also: box 10, folder 363
  - American People's Encyclopedia -- Andrews, Charles, 1923-1924, 1942, 1944-1945, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Angell, James R. (*), 1921-1925, 1929, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Angier, Roswell P. -- Arsdale, Richard van, 1914, 1942-1944, 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Anthropology Club, 1911, undated (Box 1, Folder 6a)
  - Asakawa, K. (*), 1906, 1914, 1917-1918, 1920, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ash, Dal -- Author's Guild, The, 1903, 1911, 1915-1916, 1932, 1941, 1945, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Backus, Oswald P. -- Barbour, William R., 1913-1915, 1922, 1929, 1931, 1939, 1942, 1944-1945, 1948, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bardwell, Robert D. -- Beers, Harry A., 1911, 1914-1918, 1932, 1942-1943, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Belgian Scholarship Committee -- Bennitt, Chadler, 1918, 1924, 1927, 1929, 1932, 1942, 1944, 1946, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Bensa, Francesco -- Birman, Bernard, 1914, 1932-1934, 1936, 1942, 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Bishop, Avard L. (*), 1914-1916, 1918, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    See also: box 5, folder 151
  - Bishop, Louie G. -- Bogart, John A., 1908, 1916, 1923, 1932-1933, 1940, 1943, 1945, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Boggs, Theodore H. -- Bosley, William Bradford, 1916, 1942-1943, 1945, 1949, [1907] (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Bourne, Edward Gaylord (*), 1907 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Bourne, Edward W. -- Bowman, Henry, 1929, 1933, 1937, 1943, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Bowman, Isaiah, 1926, 1935-1936, 1945, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    See also: box 14, folder 559
  - Brackett, Haven D., 1915 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Brady, Tom P., 1943, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Brady, Tom P., 1949-1951 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    See also: box 5, folder 173
  - Brandt & Brandt -- Brown, Cyril, 1914, 1916, 1934, 1940, 1943, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Brown, Esther Lucille -- Bulkeley, R. T., 1914, 1916, 1932-1933, 1937, 1943-1944, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Bull, F. Kingsbury -- Byrd, Harry F., 1915, 1917, 1923, 1941-1943, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Bullitt, William C., Jr. (Box 1, Folder 24)
    See also: box 13, folder 526 See also: box 50, folder 1317
  - Cahn, Bertram J. -- Campbell, Douglass, 1942, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Campbell, F. L., 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Canadian Civil Service Commission -- Celentano, William C., 1929, 1933, 1939-1941, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Chamberlain, John R. (*), 1935, 1944, 1950-1953 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    See also: box 4, folder 133
  - Chamberlain, Robert -- Chase, Edward E., 1915, 1940, 1943-1945, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Cheney, B. Austin, Dr. (*), 1916, 1918, 1931, 1935-1945, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
    See also: box 1, folder 27
  - Cheney, Howell (*), 1932, 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Cherry, Alfred F. -- Chisholm, Agnes, 1931, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Chisholm, R. W. (*), 1943-1944, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Chittenden, R. H., 1916, 1918-1919, 1921 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Clapp, E. J. -- A. Coburn, 1915-1916, 1933, 1936-1937, 1942, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Coe, Ralph, 1944-1945, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Coffin, C. P. -- Coleman, Christopher B., 1911, 1915, 1934, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Coit, Margaret L., 1950 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Coleman, R. V., 1926-1928 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    See also: box 14, folder 576-577
  - Coles, Marvin -- Copp, Elizabeth A., 1915, 1918, 1927, 1933, 1941-1946 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Corbin, Arthur L., 1924, 1942, 1944, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Corwin, Robert N. -- Coss, John J., 1924, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Coulter, Charles W., 1915-1916, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Coward -- McCann -- Cronan, James P., 1914, 1931, 1942-1943, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Cross, Wilbur L., 1916, 1922-1925,1928, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    See also: box 50, folder 1329
  - Crowell, Robert L. (*), 1942-1943 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    See also: box 26, folder 755-763
  - Culbertson, W. S. -- Cushing, J. P., 1915, 1942-1948, undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Cutler, J. E. (*), 1910, 1914-1916 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Cutler, J. E. (*), 1917-1918, 1933, 1937, 1942-1944, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Daeker, K., 1931-1932, 1935, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Daggett, David L. -- Dana, J. Dwight, 1910, 1913, 1916, 1942, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Danaher, John A. (*), 1940-1943 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Daniels, W. M. -- Davenport, Marcia, 1924, 1942, 1947, 1953-1954 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Davidson, Eugene A. (*), 1929-1931 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Davidson, Eugene A. (*), 1932-1939, 1945, undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
    See also: box 14, folder 578 See also: box 23, folder 722-730
  - Davidson, John C., 1942 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Davie, Maurice R. (*), 1916, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Davie, Maurice R. (*), 1924, undated, 1926, 1935, 1937-1939, 1941-1943, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Davis, Malcolm W., 1928-1931 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    See also: box 14, folder 578
  - Day, Clarence, Jr., 1903-1905 (Box 2, Folder 59-60)
  - Day, Clarence, Jr. (*), 1906, 1907 January-1906 April (Box 2, Folder 61-62)
  - Day, Clarence, Jr., 1907 May-September (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Day, Clarence, Jr. (*), 1907 October-December (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Day, Clarence, Jr. (*), 1908 January-March (Box 2, Folder 65)
    See also: box 13, folder 517
  - Day, Clarence, Jr. (*), 1908 April-June (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Day, Clarence, Jr., 1908 July (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Day, Clarence, Jr., 1908 December (Box 2, Folder 68)
    See also: box 33, folder 819-836
  - Day, Clarence, Jr. (*), 1909 January-March (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Day, Clarence, Jr., 1909 April-May (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Day, Clarence, Jr. (*), 1909 June-December (Box 3, Folder 71-72)
  - Day, Clarence, Jr., 1910 January-September (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Day, Clarence, Jr. (*), 1911 April (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Day, Clarence, Jr., 1911 May (Box 3, Folder 75)
    See also: box 13, folder 523
  - Day, Clarence, Jr. (*), 1911 June-December (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Day, Clarence, Jr., 1912 April May (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Day, Clarence, Jr. (*), 1912 June-December (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Day, Clarence, Jr., 1913 January-Jul, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 79-80)
  - Day, Clarence, Jr.(*), 1915-1917 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    See also: box 41, folder 1140
  - Day, Clarence, Jr., 1918 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Day, Clarence, Jr. (*), 1919-1924 (Box 3, Folder 83-84)
  - Day, Clarence, Jr., 1925 January-May (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Day, Clarence, Jr., 1925 June-December (Box 3, Folder 86)
    See also: box 17, folder 622-721 See also: box 10, folder 363
  - Day, Clarence, Jr., 1925-1927 (Box 3, Folder 87-88)
  - Day, Clarence, Jr., 1928-1931 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    See also: box 23, folder 722-736
  - Day, Clarence, Jr., 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 90-91)
  - Day, Clarence, Jr., 1935 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    See also: box 37, folder 961
  - Day, Clarence, Jr., letters (*), undated (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Day, Clarence, Jr., fragments (*), undated (Box 3, Folder 94-96)
  - Day, Clarence, Jr., enclosures (*), undated (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Day, Clive, 1916-1917, 1921, 1925 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Day, George Parmly (*), 1913-1914, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Day, George Parmly (*), 1923, 1925 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    See also: box 17, folder 622-721
  - Day, George Parmly (*), 1927-1928, 1930 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Day, George Parmly (*), 1931, 1933-1939, 1942-1945 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Day, George Parmly (*), 1947-1950 (Box 4, Folder 103)
    See also: box 14, folder 574-578 See also: box 14, folder 580 See also: box 50, folder 1332-1358
  - Day, Katharine, 1939, 1948-1950 (Box 4, Folder 104)
    See also: box 9, folder 314-318
  - Dayton, John S. -- Demaria, Giovanni, 1932, 1939, 1942, 1944, 1946, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Deming, J. R. -- Didion, Frederic J., 1914, 1928, undated 1942, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Dodd, Mead & Co., 1930, 1935, 1943, undated (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Dodge, Francis P., 1915-1917 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Donaldson, Norman V., 1930-1931 (Box 4, Folder 109)
    See also: box 17, folder 622-721 See also: box 23, folder 722-730
  - Donaldson, Norman V., 1932 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Donaldson, Norman V. (*), 1937, 1940, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Donaldson, Norman V., 1943 August (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Donaldson, Norman V. (*), 1943 September-December (Box 4, Folder 113)
    See also: box 14, folder 545-546
  - Donaldson, Norman V. (*), 1944 January-April (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Donaldson, Norman V., 1944 May-1947 May (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Donaldson, Norman V. (*), 1947 June-Dec, 1948, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 116)
    See also: box 14, folder 573-578
  - Doubleday, Doran & Co., 1934, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Downes, Donald C. -- Dun, Angus, 1927, 1942-1944, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Duncklee, George W. (*), 1914, 1941-1942, 1947, 1949, undated (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Dwight, H. Stanley -- Dwinnell, Stanley, 1942, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Eagan, Edward -- Ehrmann, W. W., 1902, 1914, 1921, 1945-1948, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Einstein, Albert, 1947 February 10 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Ellery, Edward -- Evans, Theodore S., 1915-1916, 1921, 1930, 1932-1934, 1945-1948, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Fairchild, Fred Rogers, 1904, 1919-1918, 1932, 1947-1948, undated (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Fairchild, Henry Pratt, 1942, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Farnam, Elizabeth K. -- Farnam, Henry W., 1913, 1915-1917, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Farnam, Thomas W. -- Field Society, Eugene, 1905, 1932-1933, 1940-1945, 1947, undated (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Farr, Hollen (Box 4, Folder 127)
    See also: box 2, folder 60
  - Field, Minna -- Fisher, Samuel H., 1914, 1916, 1922, 1930, 1932, 1942, 1944-1945, undated (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Fitzgerald, T. -- Ford, Virginia, 1915, 1924, 1930, 1934, 1940, 1945-1946, 1955, undated (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - Fortune, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Fowler, A. W., 1916 (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Frankfurter, Felix, 1942 November 11 (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Franklin, Fabian -- Fuld, M. Ernest, 1923, 1935, 1945, 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Fuller, Clement A., 1936-1948 (Box 4, Folder 134-139)
  - Fuller, H. W. -- Furniss, E. S., 1917, 1929-1930, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 140)
  - Gabriel, Ralph Henry, 1923-1924, 1929, undated (Box 5, Folder 141)
  - Gaillard, G. Y. -- Gallup, Christopher, 1916, 1942-1943 (Box 5, Folder 142)
  - Garrison, Wendell Phillip (*), 1901-1906 (Box 5, Folder 143)
    See also: box 10, folder 376
  - Garver, John A., 1932 (Box 5, Folder 144)
  - Gemeling, Hermine, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - Gephart, W. F. -- Geyelin, Philip L., 1915, 1918, 1943, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - Gherini, Ambrose (*), 1944-1945, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - Giddings, Franklin H., 1915-1917, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 148)
  - Gillett, Phillip L. -- Gimbel, Richard, 1911, 1913, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - Ginn and Company, 1904-1905, 1912, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 150)
  - Ginn and Company (*), 1916-1918, 1923-1925, 1932, 1935-1938 (Box 5, Folder 151)
    See also: box 25, folder 736
  - Ginn and Company, 1941-1942, 1946-1948, undated (Box 5, Folder 152)
    See also: box 13, folder 532-535 See also: box 53, folder 1429
  - Carter Glass, 1934-1935, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - Glicksman, Nathan -- Gordon, L. S., Jr., 1913, 1915-1916, 1932, 1943, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Granite, Mark, 1935, 1940-1942, 1943 February (Box 5, Folder 155-157)
  - Granite, Mark (*), 1943 March April (Box 5, Folder 158)
  - Granite, Mark, 1943 May-August (Box 5, Folder 159-160)
  - Granite, Mark (*), 1943 September-December (Box 5, Folder 161)
  - Granite, Mark, 1944 January-Mar, undated (Box 5, Folder 162)
  - Granite, Mark (*), 1944 April-July (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - Granite, Mark, 1944 September-1945 November (Box 5, Folder 164-166)
  - Granite, Mark (*), 1946 (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - Granite, Mark, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 168-170)
  - Granite, Mark (*), 1948-1950, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 171-173)
  - Granite, Mark (*), undated (Box 5, Folder 174)
    See also: box 51, folder 1362-1395
  - Granniss, Robert Andrew -- Gregory, Herbert Ernest, 1915, 1919, 1942, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 175)
  - Griffin, H. W. -- Guyot, Yves, 1910, 1915-1916, 1932, 1939, 1942, 1944-1945 (Box 6, Folder 176)
  - Haas, George E. -- Haddock, John C., 1932, 1937, 1942-1943, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 177)
  - Hadley, Arthur Twining, 1910, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 178)
    See also: box 41, folder 1138
  - Haggard, Howard W. -- Harbison, John P., 1916-1917, 1929, 1932, 1939, 1942-1943, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 179)
  - Hamill, Charles H., 1928-1932 (Box 6, Folder 179)
  - Harcourt, Brace & Co., 1941-1944 (Box 6, Folder 180)
  - Harees, J. Taber -- Harold, George S., 1932, 1942, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 181)
  - Harper and Brothers (*), 1916, undated, 1919, 1929-1931, 1943, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 182)
  - Harris, Benedict R. -- Hart, Mervin K., 1916-1917, 1941-1944, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 183)
  - Hart, Thomas C. (*), 1945-1948 (Box 6, Folder 184)
  - Harvard University -- Harvey, E. D., 1937, 1947, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 185)
  - Havemeyer, Loomis, 1914-1915 (Box 6, Folder 186)
  - Hawkes, H. E., 1914-1917, 1924, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 187)
    See also: box 3, folder 80-81
  - Hawley, Jane L. -- Haywood, H. L., 1910, 1914-1916, 1933, 1942, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 188)
  - Heath & Co., D. C. -- Herod, William P., 1914, 1942-1944, 1946-1947, 1949, undated (Box 6, Folder 189)
  - Herrick, Harold Hicks, Louis L., 1916, 1929, 1940, 1942-1943, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 190)
  - Hincks, Edith Walker -- Holstein, Ted S., 1914, 1916, 1918, 1920-1921, 1942, 1944-1945, 1948-1949, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 191)
  - Holt, Henry (*), 1913-1917, 1925, 1935 (Box 6, Folder 192-193)
  - Holt, Lucius H. (*), 1916-1919, 1923 (Box 6, Folder 194)
  - Hoover, Herbert, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 195)
  - Horchaw, Reuben -- Horwill, Hubert W., 1934, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 196)
  - House, W. Watson -- Hutchins, Waldo, Jr., 1914-1916, 1924, 1926, 1935-1936, 1938, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 197)
  - Ingens, Marc -- Ives, C. P., 1913, 1922, 1937, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 198)
  - Jackson, John Day (*), 1944-1945, 1952, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 199)
  - Jastrow, Joseph, 1932-1933 (Box 6, Folder 200)
  - Johnson, Allen (*), 1916-1917, 1923, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 201)
  - Johnson, Frederic B. -- Jones, Elliott, 1913, 1918, 1921, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 202)
  - Jones, Frederick S. (*), 1914, 1916-1918, 1923, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 203)
  - Jones, Louis C. -- Jones, Ursula, 1934, 1940, 1942, 1944, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 204)
  - Judd, George E. (*), 1942-1945, 1946-1949, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 205)
  - Junior League of the Oranges, 1943-1944 (Box 6, Folder 206)
  - Junkers, Luise, 1947, 1949 February-May (Box 6, Folder 207)
  - Junkers, Luise, 1949 August-December (Box 6, Folder 208)
    See also: box 6, folder 209-217 See also: box 9, folder 336 See also: box 10, folder 382-388
  - Junkers, Selma, 1930-1936 (Box 6, Folder 209-216)
  - Junkers, Selma (*), 1937, 1939, 1947, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 217)
  - Kalm, Eugene -- Keeler, Floyd Y., 1901, 1919, 1941, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 218)
  - Keeling, Ralph F., 1938, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 219)
  - Keeling, Ralph. F., undated (Box 6, Folder 220)
  - Keller, Mrs. Albert G. (Caroline), 1909 (Box 7, Folder 221)
  - Keller, Carl T. (*), 1912-1915 (Box 7, Folder 222)
  - Keller, Carl T., 1916-1917 (Box 7, Folder 223)
  - Keller, Carl T. (*), 1932-1938 January-April (Box 7, Folder 224-233)
  - Keller, Carl T., 1938 May-December (Box 7, Folder 234)
    See also: box 25, folder 734-735
  - Keller, Carl T., 1939 January-May (Box 7, Folder 235)
  - Keller, Carl T. (*), 1939 June-December (Box 7, Folder 236)
  - Keller, Carl T. (*), 1940 January-June (Box 7, Folder 237)
    See also: box 13, folder 526-527 See also: box 51, folder 1369-1373
  - Keller, Carl T. (*), 1940 July-December (Box 7, Folder 238)
  - Keller, Carl T. (*), 1941 January-March (Box 7, Folder 239)
    See also: box 9, folder 334
  - Keller, Carl T. (*), 1941 April-October (Box 7, Folder 240-241)
  - Keller, Carl T., 1941 November-1942 January (Box 7, Folder 242-243)
  - Keller, Carl T., 1942 February (Box 7, Folder 244)
    See also: box 13, folder 526-527
  - Keller, Carl T., 1942March-April (Box 7, Folder 245-246)
  - Keller, Carl T. (*), 1942 May-July (Box 7, Folder 247)
  - Keller, Carl T., 1942 August-1943 January (Box 7, Folder 248-250)
  - Keller, Carl T. (*), 1943 February-March (Box 7, Folder 251)
  - Keller, Carl T., 1943 April-December (Box 7, Folder 252-254)
  - Keller, Carl T. (*), 1944-1945 January (Box 7, Folder 255-257)
  - Keller, Carl T., 1945 February-March (Box 7, Folder 258-259)
  - Keller, Carl T. (*), 1945 April-November (Box 7, Folder 260-262)
  - Keller, Carl T., 1945 December (Box 7, Folder 263)
  - Keller, Carl T. (*), 1946 January-June (Box 7, Folder 264-265)
  - Keller, Carl T., 1946 July-September (Box 7, Folder 266)
  - Keller, Carl T. (*), 1946 October-December (Box 7, Folder 267)
  - Keller, Carl T. (*), 1947 January-March (Box 8, Folder 268)
    See also: box 6, folder 209-217
  - Keller, Carl T. (*), 1947 April-September (Box 8, Folder 269-270)
  - Keller, Carl T., 1947 October (Box 8, Folder 271)
  - Keller, Carl T. (*), 1947 November-December (Box 8, Folder 272)
  - Keller, Carl T. (*), 1948 January-April (Box 8, Folder 273)
    See also: box 38, folder 1037-1040
  - Keller, Carl T. (*), 1948 May (Box 8, Folder 274)
  - Keller, Carl T., 1948 June-July (Box 8, Folder 275)
  - Keller, Carl T. (*), 1948 August-October (Box 8, Folder 276-277)
  - Keller, Carl T., 1948 November-1949 January (Box 8, Folder 278-279)
  - Keller, Carl T. (*), 1949 February-May (Box 8, Folder 280-281)
  - Keller, Carl T., 1949 June-September (Box 8, Folder 282-283)
  - Keller, Carl T., 1949 October (Box 8, Folder 284)
    See also: box 26, folders 764-773
  - Keller, Carl T. (*), 1949 November-December (Box 8, Folder 285)
  - Keller, Carl T., 1950 January (Box 8, Folder 286)
  - Keller, Carl T. (*), 1950 February-1951 April-June (Box 8, Folder 287-291)
  - Keller, Carl T., 1951 July-October (Box 8, Folder 292)
    See also: box 28, folder 774-790
  - Keller, Carl T. (*), 1951 November-1953 (Box 8, Folder 293-296)
  - Keller, Carl T. (*), 1954, undated (Box 8, Folder 297)
    See also: box 15, folder 590-592
  - Keller, Caroline, 1932, 1942, 1948-1949, undated (Box 8, Folder 298-299)
  - Keller, Deane, 1940, 1944, 1946, 1949, undated (Box 8, Folder 300-301)
  - Keller, Elsa, 1916 (Box 8, Folder 302)
    See also: box 10, folder 360
  - Keller, Katherine, 1941, 1945, undated (Box 8, Folder 303)
  - Keller, Louise, 1942, undated (Box 8, Folder 304)
  - Keller, Marian T., 1942 (Box 8, Folder 305)
  - Keller, Ralph H., 1944 (Box 8, Folder 306)
  - Keller, Samuel S., 1913, 1915, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 307)
  - Kellog, Elizabeth -- Kennedy, Jim, 1915, 1930, 1937, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 308)
  - Kennedy, Raymond, 1941-1942, 1947, undated (Box 8, Folder 309)
  - Kennedy, Mrs. Raymond (Ruby J.), 1949 (Box 8, Folder 310)
  - Keyes, F. -- Kilpatrick, John R., 1912, 1915, 1942-1943, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 311)
  - King, Wendell, 1942-1943, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 312)
  - Kingsbury, Susan M. -- Knollenberg, Bernard, 1916, 1923-1924, 1937, 1938, 1941-1946 (Box 8, Folder 313)
  - Knopf, Alfred A., Inc. (*), 1929, 1938, 1941-1942, 1945-1948 (Box 9, Folder 314)
  - Knopf, Alfred A., Inc., 1949 January-September (Box 9, Folder 315-316)
  - Knopf, Alfred A., Inc. (*), 1949 October-November (Box 9, Folder 317)
  - Knopf, Alfred A., Inc. (*), 1949 December-1950 (Box 9, Folder 318)
  - Knortz, Karl -- Kuppenheimer, B., 1914, 1942, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 319)
  - Ladd, Florence B. -- Lang, H. R., 1912, 1933-1934, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 320)
  - Langdon, William C. -- Lawrence, John, 1916, 1926, 1942, 1951, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 321)